intellipaat.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | Intellipaat

### Overview

We take your privacy seriously and are committed to protect your right to privacy as a user of our website. We have made every effort to ensure your information is secure. This privacy policy information covers what information is collected, what we do with it, and what you can do about it. You can use this information to make your decisions about your privacy.

### About us and the website

Intellipaat.com provides online and classroom training for big data, Hadoop ecosystem, business Intelligence, cloud technologies and other niche technologies. Our courses are designed to help participants in their professional career and clear other professional examinations conducted by different technology companies.

### Intellipaat Information Practices

Every effort has been taken to ensure the accuracy of the information on the website; the content is naturally subject to change. We are not responsible for any damages arising out of the use of the information held on this server.

We assure that all our downloadable training content is virus free. However, Intellipaat can accept no liability for damages resulting from virus infection.

### Information collected by Intellipaat

  * You have total control on the privacy of your information
  * Your information will never be sold, exchanged or disclosed to any third party ? ?for marketing purposes
  * You can decide whether you want to opt-in to receive offers from us

You can browse our website without registration. We may collect and store the information that you voluntarily disclose to us, in order to access our free tests and discussion forum. We do not share your personal information with any third party. We do not collect information about our visitors from email databases, private/ public organization or bodies.

We may use your information to contact you via email or telephone, typically to get feedback, to inform you about new products or provide support on your issues, If you do not want us to contact you via email, you can unsubscribe at any time with one click.

When you purchase our online products or register for classroom training, you need to make the payment online or offline based on convenience thus you will be required to share your personal information such as name, e-mail address, telephone number, address(s), Paypal details with us. During this program, we store your contact information in our registration and order-entry systems. Your paypal information is never stored in our system as it is processed by our payment gateway which uses Secure Encryption Technology (SSL). Our payment processing partner is PayPal.

### External Links

Our website may have links to other sites which includes third party websites or resources. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and information practices of third party websites. Please read privacy policies of third party websites as every website has different terms of use and privacy policies.

### Course Content

Course content for all the study programs online or offline trainings, it is provided for the purpose of education and guidance only. The course content is regularly reviewed and is subjected to change without notice. Intellipaat reserves the right to modify training content without notice.

### Access to Intellipaat e-learning Solution

Sharing of Intellipaat training material and e-learning credentials to your friends, family members, colleagues . Please be aware that sharing of Intellipaat training material or e-learning credentials is  strictly prohibited and can have legal implications. If anyone found sharing Intellipaat training material or e-learning credentials his/her account will be disabled permanently and will be un-enrolled from the course automatically.

### Copyright information

You can electronically copy or take print of the website pages, if it is being used for personal use only. Intellipaat holds the copyright to all thematerial on this website, unless otherwise indicated. A written permission of the copyright holder must be obtained for any use of this material other than for purposes permitted by law.

### Personal Information Policy

**Image and Video Capture**

Any images captured during events organized and hosted by Intellipaat should not be misused. That includes pictures of Intellipaat staff and training participants. If you enroll in anIntellipaat course your picture may also be featured in photos or videos of the Intellipaat classes.

**Sharing your personal information**

If you have purchased anIntellipaat course, we may ask you for testimonial and if you authorize us, we will display your testimonial on our website, photos and videos or in our social media channels such as Facebook, YouTube, etc. You should be aware that your publicly identifiable information could be used to send you promotional, unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for your personal information which you have chosen to display.

If you don’t want us to feature your pictures/testimonials on our website or on our social media channels, you can write a mail to [support@Intellipaat.com](mailto:support@Intellipaat.com)

**Personal Information Corrections**

You can contact us if you notice that the information we are holding is incorrect or incomplete. Please send us a mail to [support@Intellipaat.com ](mailto:support@Intellipaat.com)

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy terms may change time to time and we reserve the right to change the terms of this privacy policy at any time. When we update the privacy policy, all our registered users will be notified via email.

**Deleting Personal Information**

If you would like to delete your account, write to [support@Intellipaat.com ](mailto:support@Intellipaat.com)

### Privacy Policy Questions?

If you have any questions regarding Intellipaat Privacy Policy, Please write to [support@Intellipaat.com](mailto:support@Intellipaat.com)
